Guide to the Cornell University Graduate School records, 1909-2012.
Cornell University Graduate School records, 1909-2012.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Graduate School records, 1909-2012.
12-1-1776
Cornell University. Graduate School.
11 volumes; 29.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, administrative records, statistics, announcements, speeches, reports, catalogs, applications, minutes, program reviews and external reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
11 volumes of correspondence, administrative records, and statistics of the Cornell University Graduate School; also, announcements, speeches, reports, catalogs, applications, minutes, department self studies, program reviews, and external reports. Includes Graduate School annual reports for 1922 and 1952/1953-1986/1987 as well as 2001/2002-2002/2003.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
11 volumes of correspondence, administrative records, and statistics of the Cornell University Graduate School; also, announcements, speeches, reports, catalogs, applications, minutes, department self studies, program reviews, and external reports. Includes Graduate School annual reports for 1922 and 1952/1953-1986/1987 as well as 2001/2002-2002/2003. The report for 1922 is titled "Problems of the Graduate School: an informal report by the Dean, to the members of the faculty"; it was conceived of as a supplement to the annual Dean's report to the President.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Graduate School.; Cornell University--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Eight volumes of correspondence, administrative records, and statistics, 1909-1921 (Box 1-5)
- Announcements, 1892 (Box 6)
- Legislation, 1951-1971 (Box 6)
- Speeches relevant to Graduate School (Box 6)
- Committee on Graduate School Legislation, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
- Study Committee Reports, 1965 (Box 6)
- Minutes of the Faculty of the Graduate School, 1960-1976 (Box 6)
- Minutes of the Faculty of the Graduate School, 1917-1964 (Box 7)
- Code of Legislation of the Graduate Faculty, June 2001 (Box 12)
- Guide to the Graduate Study, 1993-1995, 2001-2003 (Box 12)
- Annual Report of the Graduate School, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
- Annual Report of the Graduate School, 2002-2003 (Box 12)
- Catalog, 2002-2004 (Box 12)
- A Guide for Graduate Students, 2002-2004 (Box 12)
- Doctoral Dissertations and Master's Thesis: Formatting, Production and Submission Requirements, October 1992, August 1997, June 2003 (Box 12)
- Resources for Graduate Students, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
- Application, 2004-2005 (Box 12)
- Graduate Education at Cornell (Box 12)
- AAVLD Accreditation Review for the Diagnostic Laboratory, 1997 (Box 13)
- Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science Self Study, 1999 (Box 13)
- Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science Self Study Draft, 2005 (Box 13)
- Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science Self Study Final and External Review, 2005; 2006 (Box 13)
- Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science Self Study Professorial and Non-Professorial CVs, 1999 (Box 13)
- Clinical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine Self Study, 1999 (Box 14)
- Clinical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine Appendix 2 - Professorial and Faculty CVs, 1999 (Box 14)
- Clinical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine Appendix 3 - CVs, Non-Professorial Academics, 1999 (Box 14)
- Clinical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine Addendum, 2001 (Box 14)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics - CALS Departmental Review - Appendix A: Faculty Vitae, 1999 (Box 14)
- AAP Architecture Self Study and External Review, 2006; 2007 (Box 14)
- AAP Art Self Study and External Review, 2000; 2001 (Box 15)
- History of Art Self Study, 1999 (Box 15)
- History of Art External Review, 2000 (Box 15)
- Theatre, Film, and Dance Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 15)
- Anthropology Self Study and External Review, 2000 (Box 15)
- Biochemistry Molecular and Cell Biology Self Study and External Review, 1998 (Box 15)
- Government External Review, Dean Response, 2003 (Box 16)
- Molecular Biology and Genetics Self Study, 2008 (Box 16)
- Genetics and Development Self Study and External Review, 1998; 1999 (Box 16)
- Science and Technology Studies Self Study, 2000 (Box 16)
- Laboratory of Ornithology Self Study, 2008 (Box 16)
- Laboratory of Ornithology External Review, 1999 (Box 16)
- Astronomy Self Study and External Review, 2004 (Box 16)
- Mathematics Self Study and External Review, 2003; 2004 (Box 16)
- Sage School of Philosophy Self Study and External Review, 2003 (Box 17)
- Near Eastern Studies Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 17)
- Comparative Literature Self Study and External Review, 2002; 2003 (Box 17)
- Romance Studies Self Study and External Review, 2003 (Box 17)
- CIPA Cornell Institute of Public Affairs Self Study Vol. I, 2008 (Box 17)
- CIPA Supporting Documentation Vol. II, 2008 (Box 17)
- CIPA Publications Volume III, 2008 (Box 17)
- Computer Science Self Study and External Review, 1998 (Box 18)
- Computer Science Self Study, 2007 (Box 18)
- Social Sciences External Advisory Council Internal and External Report, 2007 (Box 18)
- Natural Resources Self Study Vol. I, 1999 (Box 18)
- Natural Resources Vol. II: Appendices, 1999 (Box 18)
- Natural Resources External Review, 2000 (Box 18)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture Self Study, 2000 (Box 18)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture External Review, 2000 (Box 18)
- Agricultural and Biological Engineering Self Study, 2000; 2001 (Box 18)
- Policy Analysis and Management Self Study, 2004 (Box 18)
- Design and Environmental Analysis Self Study, 2004 (Box 18)
- Design and Environmental Analysis External Review, 2004 (Box 18)
- Textiles and Apparel Self Study, 2003 (Box 19)
- Textiles and Apparel External Review, 2004 (Box 19)
- Proposal for PhD Degree in Apparel Design in the Field of Textiles, 2009 (Box 19)
- Sociology Self Study, 2000 (Box 19)
- Sociology External Review, 2001 (Box 19)
- Sociology Self Study, 2009 (Box 19)
- Development Sociology Self Study, 2007 (Box 19)
- Animal Science Self Study and External Review, 1999 (Box 20)
- Animal Science Self Study (Draft), 2009 (Box 20)
- Animal Science Self Study (Final), 2009 (Box 20)
- Food Science Ithaca, NY Self Study, 1994 (Box 20)
- Food Science Collaborative Programs at Ithaca and Geneva Self Study, 1994 (Box 20)
- Food Science and Technology Geneva, NY Self Study, 1994 (Box 20)
- Communication External Review, 2000; 2003 (Box 20)
- Communication Self Study, 2010 (Box 20)
- Economics Self Study Part 1, 1999 (Box 21)
- Economics Self Study Part 2, 1999 (Box 21)
- Economics Dean Response to External Review, 2003 (Box 21)
- City and Regional Planning Appendix A Faculty Vitae, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
- City and Regional Planning Appendix B Part 1 Course Syllabi, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
- City and Regional Planning Appendix B Part 2 Course Syllabi, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
- City and Regional Planning Self Study and Special Reports, 2002 (Box 21)
- Briefing Book: Proposal to Dissolve the College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 2002 (Box 21)
- Linguistics Self Study and External Review, 1999; 2008 (Box 21)
- Hotel Administration PhD Program - Periodic Statewide Doctoral Program Review Stage II - Goals, Resources, and Quality, 2001 (Box 22)
- Hotel Administration Doctoral Review Stage II - Appendix A: Faculty Information, 2001 (Box 22)
- Hotel Administration PhD Program - Periodic Statewide Doctoral Program Review Stage II - Student and Program Information, Appendices B, C, and D, 2001 (Box 22)
- Asian Studies Self Study and Department Response, 2009 (Box 22)
- Asian Studies External Review and Department Reponse, 2002; 2003 (Box 22)
- Africana Studies and Research Center Self Study and External Review, 2005 (Box 22)
- German Studies Self Study and External Review, 2001; 2002 (Box 22)
- German Cultural Studies Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 22)
- Education Self Study, 2000 (Box 22)
- Education External Review, 2000 (Box 22)
- Civil and Environmental Engineering Self Study and External Review, 2006 (Box 23)
- Materials Science and Engineering Self Study and External Review, 2004 (Box 23)
- Applied and Engineering Physics Self Study, 2004 (Box 23)
- Applied and Engineering Physics External Review, 2005 (Box 23)
- Architecture Self Study, 2006-2007 (Box 23)
- Landscape Architects Program Self Study, 1997 (Box 23)
- Landscape Architecture Self Evaluation Report, 2008 (Box 23)
- Real Estate Self Study, 2009 (Box 23)
- Enaudi Center External Review, 2001 (Box 23)
- "Orphan" External Review Reports (Box 23)
- Program Review Closing Checklist, 1999 (Box 23)
- Fruit and Vegetable Science, Ithaca, and Horticultural Sciences, Geneva, Self Study, 1999 (Box 24)
- Fruit and Vegetable Science External Review, 1999 (Box 24)
- Crop and Soil Science External Review, 2001 (Box 24)
- Ecology and Evolutionary Biology Self Study and External Review, 2007 (Box 24)
- Psychology Self Study and External Review, 2001 (Box 24)
- Psychology Self Study and External Review, 2008 (Box 24)
- English Department Self Study and External Review, 2003; 2004 (Box 24)
- Ecology and Systematics Self Study and External Review, 1999 (Box 25)
- Music Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 25)
- ILR School Self Study, 2007 (Box 25)
- Neurobiology and Behavior Self Study and External Review, 1998 (Box 25)
- Neurobiology and Behavior Self Study, 2007 (Box 25)
- Family Life Development Center, College of Human Ecology, Self Study and External Review, 2005 (Box 25)
- L. H. Bailey Hortorium Comprehensive Review, 1988 (Box 26)
- L. H. Bailey Hortorium and Plant Biology Self Study and External Review, 1998 (Box 26)
- Cornell University Press Self Study (Draft), 2003 (Box 26)
- Cornell University Press Self Study (Final), 2003 (Box 26)
- Cornell University Press Appendices (Box 26)
- Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering Self Study and External Review, 2005 (Box 26)
- Baker Institute for Animal Health Self Study, 2003 (Box 26)
- Operations Research and Industrial Engineering Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 27)
- Electrical and Computer Engineering Self Study, 2007 (Box 27)
- Electrical Engineering External Review, 1998 (Box 27)
- Microbiology and Immunology Self Study and External Review, 1999 (Box 27)
- Molecular Medicine Self Study and External Review, 2006 (Box 27)
- Entomology Self Study, 1996 (Box 27)
- Entomology Self Study and External Review, 2006 (Box 27)
- Microbiology Self Study, 1998 (Box 27)
- Theoretical and Applied Mechanics Self Studies and External Review, 1999; 2000 (Box 27)
- Biomedical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine CVs, Professorial, 2000 (Box 28)
- Human Development Self Study, 2007 (Box 28)
- Biomedical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine Self Study and External Review, 2000 (Box 29)
- Biomedical Sciences, College of Veterinary Medicine CVs, Non-Professorial, 2000 (Box 29)
- Chemistry and Chemical Biology Self Study, 2001 (Box 29)
- Chemistry and Biomolecular Engineering Self Study and External Review, 2002; 2003 (Box 29)
- Physics Self Study and External Review, 2004; 2005 (Box 29)
- Plant Biology Self Study, 1998 (Box 30)
- Plant Biology External Review (Box 30)
- Plant Breeding and Genetics Self Study, 2008 (Box 30)
- Plant Pathology, Ithaca and Geneva, Self Study - A Comprehensive Review, 1999 (Box 30)
- Plant Pathology, Ithaca and Geneva, External Review, 1999 (Box 30)
- Plant Pathology and Plant-Microbe Biology, Ithaca and Geneva, Self Study, 2008 (Box 30)
- Applied Economics and Management Self Study and PhD Changes, 2008; 2009 (Box 30)
- Law School Self Study and External Review, 2005-2006 (Box 30)
- CIFAD Self Study, 2000 (Box 30)
- CIFAD Response to External Review, 2001 (Box 30)
- Reorganizing the Biological Sciences at Cornell, 2000 (Box 30)
- Society for the Humanities Self Study and External Review, 2005; 2006 (Box 31)
- History Self Study, 2000 (Box 31)
- History External Review, 2000 (Box 31)
- History Faculty CVs, 2000 (Box 31)
- Rural Sociology Self Study, 1997 (Box 31)
- Nutritional Sciences Vol. 1: Self Study, 1999 (Box 31)
- Nutritional Sciences Faculty Committee on Program Review - External Review, 1999 (Box 31)
- Physiology Self Study, 1998 (Box 31)
- Physiology Self Study, 1999 (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study, 1999 (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix B (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix C (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix D (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix E (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix F (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study Appendix H (Box 31)
- Agricultural, Resource, and Managerial Economics Self Study External Review, 1999 (Box 31)
- International Teaching Assistant Development Program Self Study, 2003-2004 (Box 31)
- External Life Sciences Advisory Council, 2002 (Box 31)
- Feminist, Gender, and Sexuality Studies Self Study and Appendices, 2006 (Box 32)
- Classics Self Study and External Review, 2002 (Box 32)
- Food Science and Technology-Geneva-Self Study, 2004 (Box 33)
- Family Life Development Center-Self Study, 2005 (Box 33)
- Department of Clinical Sciences- Veterinary School-Self Study, 2012 (Box 33)
- Index cards arranged by subject that reference particular volumes of committee minutes and 3 cassette tapes of 1994 general committee meetings (Box 34)
- Annual Reports, 1975-1987 (Box 35)
- Annual Reports, 1922, 1952-1975 (Box 36)